NATTHAPHONG JAROENPRONPRASIT

jaroenpronprasit@gmail.com 094-324-8965

SUMMARY

Backend Developer with 1 year of experience in developing various types of applications. Skilled in a wide range of technologies and eager to contribute to challenging projects. Enjoys learning new things and works well with team members.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer Prior Solution Co., Ltd.

November 2023 - Present

- Developed backend APIs for the KSAS bond trading application using Java Spring Boot, Redis, and PostgreSQL databases. Implemented file storage on AWS S3 and utilized AWS SQS for message queue management.
- Developed backend APIs for the Aurora gold trading application using Go Fiber, Redis, and PostgreSQL databases. Integrated file storage on AWS S3. Implemented WebSockets for realtime updates and Kafka for message queue management.

Backend Developer (Co-op) Prior Solution Co., Ltd.

May 2023 -October 2023

- Worked on backend bug fixes and maintenance for the PPI domestic index monitoring application, built with Java Spring Boot and Oracle database.
- Developed backend APIs for the Autosale application using Java Spring Boot, Redis, and MSSQL databases. The application facilitated car sales management for sales representatives and stored customer information.

EDUCATION

Sep 2020 - Apr 2024

Silpakorn University in computer science **GPA:**3.52

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Language: java,go,js,tsx,rust
- Frameworks: Spring Boot, Gin, Fiber, (React)
- DevOps: Jenkins, Kubernetes, Docker
- Cloud: AWS (S3, OpenSearch, EC2, SQS, SNS, Lambda)
- Databases: PostgreSQL, Oracle, Elasticsearch, Redis, MySQL, MSSQL